Guide to the Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, 40th Anniversary Documentary
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, 40th anniversary documentary
2011
SC1130
Stanford University. Program in Human Biology.
400384 megabyte(s) (83 files in 21 directories)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Access Terms
Barr, Donald A.; Bernfield, Audrey; Blumberg, Baruch.; Boggs, Carol A.; Dornbusch, Sanford M.; Durham, William H.; Ehrlich, Paul R.; Feldman, S. Shirley.; Fernald, Russell; Hamburg, David A., 1925-; Hastorf, Albert H., 1920-; Heller, H. Craig.; Katchadourian, Herant A.; Kennedy, Donald, 1931-; Klein, Richard.; Lee, Phil.; Seligo, Carlos; Siegel, Robert.; Simon, Tibby.; Wine, Jeffrey.; Wolf, Arthur P.; Human biology; Lectures.; Science--Study and teaching.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Audiovisual recordings, 2011
  - 40th Reunion Documentary + 20th Panel, 2011; 7 computer file(s)
  - Barr, Donald A., 2011; 9 computer file(s)
  - Bernfield, Audrey, 2011; 1 computer file(s)
  - Blumberg, Baruch, 2011; 2 computer file(s)
  - Boggs, Carol A., 2011; 3 computer file(s)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford M., 2011; 4 computer file(s)
  - Durham, Bill, 2011; 4 computer file(s)
  - Ehrlich, Paul R., 2011; 4 computer file(s)
  - Feldman, S. Shirley, 2011; 4 computer file(s)
  - Fernald, Russ, 2011; 3 computer file(s)
  - Hamburg, David A., 2011; 3 computer file(s)
  - Hastorf, Albert H., 2011; 5 computer file(s)
  - Heller, H. Craig, 2011; 5 computer file(s)
  - Katchadourian, Herant A., 2011; 5 computer file(s)
  - Kennedy, Donald, 2011; 4 computer file(s)
  - Klein, Richard, 2011; 3 computer file(s)
  - Lee, Phil, 2011; 1 computer file(s)
  - Siegel, Robert, 2011; 3 computer file(s)
  - Simon, Tibby, 3 computer file(s)
  - Wine, Jeffrey, 2011; 2 computer file(s)
  - Wolf, Arthur P., 2011; 4 computer file(s)